funeducation.com 2017-06-06

# FunEducation, Inc. Privacy Statement

General Privacy Statement  |  Children's Privacy Policy

* * *

FunEducation, Inc. Privacy Statement

FunEducation, and its affiliated companies including Bright Education (collectively referred to as "FunEducation") fully respects your rights to privacy and developed this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following privacy policy discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the funeducation.com Web site and any subdomains, such as brighted.funeducation.com (the "Site").

  * INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
  * REGISTRATION
  * ORDER
  * CONTESTS AND SURVEYS
  * SPECIAL OFFERS
  * PROFILE
  * CONSENT TO THE USE OF THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS
  * COOKIES
  * LOG FILES
  * CLEAR GIFS
  * CUSTOMER SERVICE
  * AGGREGATE INFORMATION
  * TELL A FRIEND
  * SECURITY PROCEDURES
  * OPT-OUT POLICY
  * CORRECTING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION
  * CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

In order to fulfill licensing transactions or provide service to you as a customer of FunEducation, we may require you to provide certain information to us. Common items may include, but are not limited to, your name, address, phone number and credit card number. By providing this information, you are agreeing to allow us to utilize this information to complete all transactions you request through this Site and to disclose that information and details of all such transactions to our subsidiaries, affiliates or necessary payment processors. 

Here is an explanation of the information we gather and how it is used: 

**REGISTRATION**

The Site's registration form gathers contact information (e.g., your name and address), unique identifiers (e.g., your e-mail address) and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). We use contact information from the registration form to send you important updates about new features on the Site and special offers from our affiliates. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you if we have a question about your registration. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt-Out Policy below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our Site. We use this data to tailor your experience at our Site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in and displaying the content according to your preferences. This information is shared with our affiliates on an aggregate basis. 

**ORDER**

The Site uses an order form to request products and services. We collect contact information (e.g., your shipping address), unique identifiers (e.g., your name and telephone number), financial information (e.g., your credit card number), and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Contact information from the order form is used to process orders and is also used to get in touch with you if there is a question about your order. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt-Out Policy below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill you for products and services. Unique identifiers (e.g., your billing address) are collected to verify your identity and protect against fraud. We keep a purchase history for each user, tracking all purchases made on the Site. We use this information to provide a high level of customer service, help you track your orders and offer personalized products and content that we think you would find helpful. Demographic and profile data is also collected during the checkout process. 

**CONTESTS AND SURVEYS**

We run contests and conduct surveys on our Site where we will obtain contact information (e.g. your email address) and demographic information (e.g. your zip code). We use contact data from our contests and surveys to send visitors information about our company, to notify winners and award prizes, and to monitor and improve the use and satisfaction of this Site. Participation in these contests or surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt-Out Policy below. 

**SPECIAL OFFERS**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications; see the Opt-Out Policy below. 

**PROFILE**

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and third party sources to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

  Supplementation of Information   
In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources such as: 

  Address Verification  
We use third party software to verify your address, in order to send you future updates, promotions and information. 

  Enhancement of Profile Information  
We purchase marketing data from third parties and add it to our existing user database, to better target our advertising and to provide pertinent offers in which we think you would be interested.  To enrich our Profiles of individual customers, we tie this information to the personally identifiable information they have provided to us.  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**CONSENT TO THE USE OF THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS**

FunEducation may contract with other third parties to provide various outsourced services to us relating to the Site rather than performing the services itself. For example, we may contract with an email provider to handle the delivery of email messages to you. Likewise, we may contract with a web site hosting provider to host the Site for us. By visiting the Site, you consent to FunEducation providing all information (whether or not personally identifiable) received or collected from you to such third party providers for the purpose of enabling the third party provider to provide these outsourced services to us. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this Site and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

Third parties will protect your information as FunEducation would under the terms of this policy. We may also share personally identifiable information with third party providers for the purpose of direct marketing, including email marketing. All third parties are bound by applicable laws including, but not limited to the CAN SPAM Act (s.877) of 2003, and are required to be in full compliance of all consumer opt-out rules and regulations. 

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

  We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

**LOG FILES**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

  We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information to track and store testing results. 

**CLEAR GIFS** (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We may tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

  We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Opt-Out Policy.” 

**CUSTOMER SERVICE**

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we may send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION**

We share demographic data, sales, traffic patterns and related site information with our affiliates and other reputable third parties in aggregate form only. The shared aggregate data does not include any personal information. 

**TELL A FRIEND**

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about our Site, we will ask you for the friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the Site. We use this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. We do not store, rent, sell or trade these e-mail addresses. 

**SECURITY PROCEDURES**

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All information is stored in a secure database behind a firewall designed to prevent unauthorized access and none of the information can be retrieved via the Internet.

To provide you with an additional layer of security, all credit card numbers are stored on a computer that is not connected to the Internet. After you type in your credit card number, it is transferred to our secure computer. This computer is not accessible by network or modem and your credit card number is not stored anywhere else except for normal back-ups. In addition, all credit card numbers stored in the secure computer are encrypted as an added security measure.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**OPT-OUT POLICY**

Our Site gives users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential communications from FunEducation. You can opt-out of receiving non-essential communications from us at any time by emailing us at  . In addition, whenever we send you a non-essential email communication, you can opt-out of similar future mailings by simply clicking on a link provided in the e-mail message.

If at any time you believe that we have not followed this Privacy Policy, you have any questions about this policy, or if you would like your information to be removed from our system, please contact us at  . We will make reasonable efforts to identify and correct any reported problems. 

**CORRECTING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION**

If you would like to revise the information provided to us, or feel that what we currently have on record is incorrect, you may update the information by emailing us at  . 

**CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

<  Back to Homepage
